Guide to the Jerome T. Barrett Collection, 1913-2010 LAC0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Jerome T. Barrett Collection
1913-2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Barrett, Jerome T.
LAC0007
135 Linear Feet
This collection contains material amassed by Jerome T. Barrett pertaining to his career as a labor mediator and commissioner and director of the Office of Technical Services of the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service. There are also materials related to the United States Consilitation Service (USCS) founded in the Department of Labor in 1913. The material dates between 1913-2013.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material amassed by Jerome T. Barrett pertaining to his career as a labor mediator and director of the Office of Technical Services of the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service. The material dates between 1913-2013. Included are oral history interviews, articles, handbooks, and annual reports. Please note that this collection is only partially processed.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Jerome T. Barrett, 2012 (2012.016)
Biographical / Historical
Jerome T. Barrett was born in 1932 in St. Paul, Minnesota. He received his Bachelors degree from the College of St. Thomas (1959) and his Masters degree from the University of Minnesota (1963). His Doctorate of Education is from The George Washington University (1984). Barrett worked as a field examiner for the National Labor Relations Board from 1961 to 1963. Following that he worked for one year as a mediator at the Minnesota Office of Labor Conciliator. He served as a mediator for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service in District of Columbia and Milwaukee from 1964 to 1969. He was assistant director of Alternative Dispute Resolution and Mediation at the National Center for Dispute Resolution, 1969 to 1970. Barrett returned to government service in 1970 as chief of the Division of Public Employee Relations at the U.S. Department of Labor. He rejoined the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service in 1973 as director of the Office of Technical Services. He taught labor relations at Northern Kentucky University from 1982 to 1985 and was an industrial relations specialist for the Department of Labor's Bureau of Labor-Management Cooperative Programs until his retirement in 1990. He is the author of over 200 published articles and papers. He is co-author of Interest Based Bargaining: A User Guide (2005) and P.A.S.T. Is the Future: A Model for Interest-Based Collective Bargaining(1998) and author of A History of Alternative Dispute Resolution (2004). He is a member of numerous mediation and arbitration-related professional associations. He passed away on November 5, 2020.
Related Materials
For additional material please see the Friends of Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service History website operated by Jerome T. Barrett - http://www.mediationhistory.org/index.html.
Conflict resolution; Labor; Dispute resolution (Law); Labor and laboring classes; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions
- The Friends of Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service History Archive, 1919-2010; Record Group 1; 68.5 Linear Feet
  Biographical / Historical
  The Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service was established as an independent government agency in 1947. Its mission is to prevent or minimize the impact of labor-management disputes by providing mediation, conciliation and voluntary arbitration. Its predecessor organization, the U. S. Conciliation Service, was established in 1918 within the Department of Labor.
  The Friends of FMCS History was founded by Dr. Jerome T. Barrett in 1992. Its purpose was to gather, preserve and publicize the history of the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service and its predecessor, the U.S. Conciliation Service. Dr. Barrett began collecting materials relating to FMCS and USCS history in the spring of 1964. Former commissioners and other FMCS staff would hand over their own history-related materials as they retired and Dr. Barrett would save materials as they were being readied for disposal. He conducted interviews with mediators as part of his doctoral dissertation and these became part of the Friends Archive. The Friends Archive was transferred to the Special Collections Research Center in 2011 and 2012.
  - Directors and Commissioners, 1919-2010; Record Group 1 Series 1; 17 Linear Feet
    - FMCS Director Files, 1942-2010; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1; 3.5 Linear Feet
      Arrangement
      This subseries is arranged according to its original order. Roughly chronological, the subseries starts with materials from the FMCS's first Director, Cyrus Ching, and goes through to John Calhoun Wells.
      Note: The order of materials restarts with Box 78 Folder 9, as these materials were added after initial processing. They follow the same arrangement pattern.
      Scope and Contents
      This subseries contains materials produced by or directly related to FMCS Directors (and Acting Directors) from 1942-2010. Included are materials from Cyrus Ching, James Greenwood, Whitely McCoy, Joseph Finnegan, William Simkin, J. Curtis Counts, William Usery, Jr., James Scearce, Wayne Horvitz, Kenneth Moffett, Kay McMurray, Bernard DeLury, Brian Flores, John Calhoun Wells, Richard Barnes, Peter Hurtgen, Scot Beckenbaugh, and George Cohen.
      The materials in this subseries vary widely. Included are internal memoranda, correspondence, reports, press releases and news clippings, as well as articles and speeches by FMCS Directors and Commissioners. This subseries' "General" folders also contain a variety of miscellaneous materials.
      - Cyrus Ching - Correspondence, 1942-1967; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Cyrus Ching - Eightieth Birthday Materials, 1956, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Cyrus Ching - Eightieth Birthday Materials and Interviews, 1956-1965; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Cyrus Ching - Family History, 1966-1989; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Cyrus Ching - Jerome Barrett "Interview", 1997; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Cyrus Ching - Ninetieth Birthday Materials, 1966; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Cyrus Ching - General, 1947-1988; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - James Greenwood - Correspondence [1/2], 1953-1954; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - James Greenwood - Correspondence [2/2], 1953-1954; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - James Greenwood - General, 1950-1951; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Whitley McCoy - General, 1953-1954; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Joseph Finnegan - General, 1956-1959; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - William Simkin - General, 1962-1985; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - J. Curtis Counts - Biographical Information, undated; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - J. Curtis Counts - Memoranda [1/3], 1970-1971; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - J. Curtis Counts - Memoranda [2/3], 1971-1972; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - J. Curtis Counts - Memoranda [3/3], 1972-1973; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - J. Curtis Counts - Press, 1969-1970; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - William Usery, Jr. - General [1/3], 1970-1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - William Usery, Jr. - General [2/3], 1973-1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - William Usery, Jr. - General [3/3], 1973-1978; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - James Scearce - General, 1976-1977; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Wayne Horvitz - General [1/2], 1980-1981; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Wayne Horvitz - General [2/2], 1979-1985; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Wayne Horvitz - Memos and Correspondence [1/3], 1977-1980; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Wayne Horvitz - Memos and Correspondence [2/3], 1977-1981; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Wayne Horvitz - Memos and Correspondence [3/3], 1976-1981; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Kenneth Moffett - General, 1973-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 4)
      - Kay McMurray - Memoranda and Reports [1/7], 1983-1988; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 75, Folder 5)
      - Kay McMurray - Memoranda and Reports [2/7], 1984-1989; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 1)
      - Kay McMurray - Memoranda and Reports [3/7], 1982-1988; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 2)
      - Kay McMurray - Memoranda and Reports [4/7], 1982-1988; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 3)
      - Kay McMurray - Memoranda and Reports [5/7], 1984-1987; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 4)
      - Kay McMurray - Memoranda and Reports [6/7], 1983-1985; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 76, Folder 5)
      - Kay McMurray - Memoranda and Reports [7/7], 1979-1988; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Kay McMurray - General, 1985-1987; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Bernard DeLury - Memoranda and Reports [1/3], 1990-1993; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Bernard DeLury - Memoranda and Reports [2/3], 1990-1993; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Bernard DeLury - Memoranda and Reports [3/3], 1991-1993; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Brian Flores - General, 1993-1996; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - John Calhoun Wells - Memos and Correspondence [1/2], 1993-1995; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - John Calhoun Wells - Memos and Correspondence [2/2], 1993-1998; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - John Calhoun Wells - General [1/3], 1991-1996; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - John Calhoun Wells - General [2/3], 1997; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - John Calhoun Wells - General [3/3], 1996-1997; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Richard Barnes - General, 1999-2002; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Peter Hurtgen - General, 2001-2004; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Scot Beckenbaugh - General, 2005; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - George Cohen - General, 2010; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - Cyrus Ching Speech, undated; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - David Cole - "Government in the Bargaining Process: The Role of the Mediator", 1961 January; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - J. Curtis Counts - Speeches, 1966-1972; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - William Usery, Jr. - Speeches, 1973-1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - Speeches-William Simkin, 1961; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 1)
      - Speeches-William Simkin, 1962; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 2)
      - Speeches-William Simkin, 1962; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 3)
      - Speeches-William Simkin, 1963; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 4)
      - Speeches-William Simkin, 1964; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 5)
      - Speeches-William Simkin, 1965; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 6)
      - Speeches-William Simkin, 1966; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 7)
      - Speeches-Morris L. Myers, 1967; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 8)
      - Speeches-William Simkin, 1968; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 9)
      - Speeches-J. Curtis Counts & Kenneth Moffett, 1969; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 10)
      - Speeches-J. Curtis Counts & Kenneth Moffett, 1970; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 11)
      - Speeches-J. Curtis Counts & Kenneth Moffett, 1971; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 12)
      - Speeches-J. Curtis Counts & W. J. Usery Jr., 1972; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 271, Folder 13)
      - Speeches-W. J. Usery Jr., March-April, 1973; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 272, Folder 1)
      - Speeches-W. J. Usery Jr., May, 1973; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 272, Folder 2)
      - Speeches-W. J. Usery Jr., July, 1973; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 272, Folder 3)
      - Speeches-W. J. Usery Jr. & Robert W. Donnahoo, August-September, 1973; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 272, Folder 4)
      - Speeches- [1 of 2] W. J. Usery Jr., October, 1973; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 272, Folder 5)
      - Speeches- [2 of 2] W. J. Usery Jr., October, 1973; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 272, Folder 6)
      - Speeches- [1 of 2] W. J. Usery Jr., November, 1973; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 272, Folder 7)
      - Speeches- [2 of 2] W. J. Usery Jr., November, 1973; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 272, Folder 8)
      - Speeches- W. J. Usery Jr., December, 1973; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 272, Folder 9)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., January, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 273, Folder 1)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., February, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 273, Folder 2)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., March, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 273, Folder 3)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., April, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 273, Folder 4)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., May, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 273, Folder 5)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., June, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 273, Folder 6)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., July, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 273, Folder 7)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., August, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 273, Folder 8)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., September, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - Speeches [1 of 2]-W.J. Usery Jr., October, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 274, Folder 2)
      - Speeches [1 of 2]-W.J. Usery Jr., October, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 274, Folder 3)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr. & Kenneth E. Moffett, November, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 274, Folder 4)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., January, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 274, Folder 5)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., March, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 274, Folder 6)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., April, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 274, Folder 7)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., May, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 275, Folder 1)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., June, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 275, Folder 2)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., July, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 275, Folder 3)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., August, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 275, Folder 4)
      - Speeches-W.J. Usery Jr., September, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 275, Folder 5)
      - Speeches [1 of 2]-W.J. Usery Jr., October, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 275, Folder 6)
      - Speeches [2 of 2]-Kenneth E. Moffett & W.J. Usery Jr., October, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 275, Folder 7)
      - Speeches [1 of 2] W.J. Usery Jr., November, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 275, Folder 8)
      - Speeches [2 of 2] W.J. Usery Jr., November, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 276, Folder 1)
      - Speeches- W.J. Usery Jr., December, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 276, Folder 2)
      - Speeches- James F. Scearce, April, 1976; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 276, Folder 3)
      - Speeches- James F. Scearce, June, 1976; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 276, Folder 4)
      - Speeches- James F. Scearce, August, 1976; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 276, Folder 5)
      - Speeches- James F. Scearce, September, 1976; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 276, Folder 6)
      - Speeches- James F. Scearce, October, 1976; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 276, Folder 7)
      - Speeches- James F. Scearce, November, 1976; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 276, Folder 8)
      - Speeches- Wayne L. Horvitz, May-September, 1977; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 276, Folder 9)
      - Speeches- Wayne L. Horvitz, November, 1977; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 276, Folder 10)
      - Speeches- Wayne L. Horvitz, November, 1977; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 276, Folder 11)
      - Speeches-Multiple Annotated Lists, 1961-1973; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 1)
      - Speeches-Wayne L. Horvitz, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 3)
      - Speeches-Wayne L. Horvitz, January, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 4)
      - Speeches-Wayne L. Horvitz & Kenneth E. Moffett, April-December, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 5)
      - Speeches-Wayne L. Horvitz, January-November, 1980; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 6)
      - Speeches-Kenneth E. Moffett, 1981; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 7)
      - Speeches-Kay McMurray, November-December, 1983; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 8)
      - Speeches-Kay McMurray & Wayne L. Horvitz, January-December, 1984; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 9)
      - Speeches-Kay McMurray, 1987; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 10)
      - Speeches-Wayne L. Horvitz, May 20-21, 1993; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 11)
      - Speeches-Wayne L. Horvitz, October 29, 1997; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 12)
      - Speeches-Peter J. Hurtgen, November 13, 2003; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 13)
      - Speeches-Peter J. Hurtgen, April 14, 2004; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 1 (Box 277, Folder 14)
    - Oral History Interviews, 1965 October 20 - 2012 April 24; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2; 6 Linear Feet
      This subseries contains typed transcripts and cassette recordings of 192 oral history interviews conducted by Jerome Barrett on behalf of the Friends of the Federal Mediation and Concilation Service History between the years of 1983 and 2012. Among those interviewed are numerous former FMCS directors, including founding director Cyrus Ching. Interview topics include biographical information, the organization and operation of the FMCS, and personal accounts of important labor disputes, including the U.S. Postal Strike of 1970. Seventeen interviews were conducted by Martha Ross and fifteen were conducted by othjer interviewers.
      This subseries is arranged alphabetically by the name of the person being interviewed. Multiple interviews of the same person are arranged chronologically, and when both a transcript and sound recording of the same interview are included the transcript is listed first.
      - George Albu, 20 February 2009; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 1)
      - Frank Allen, 11 October 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 2)
      - Steve Anderson, 20 February 2009; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 3)
      - Larry Babcock, 26 May 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Larry Babcock [1/2], 21 January 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 4)
      - Larry Babcock [2/2], 21 January 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 5)
      - Bob Barker [1/2], 24 February 1988; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 6)
      - Bob Barker [2/2], 24 February 1988; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 7)
      - Gene Barry [1/2], 17 October 1984; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 8)
      - Gene Barry [2/2], 17 October 1984; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 9)
      - Charles Baumgardner [1/2], 11 August 1984; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 10)
      - Charles Baumgardner [2/2], 11 August 1984; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 11)
      - Bob Bennett, 28 February 2011; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 12)
      - Bob Bergstrom, 19 March 1985; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Bob Bergstrom, 19 March 1985; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 13)
      - Bob Berman, 24 April 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 14)
      - Joe Biondo, 2 October 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 15)
      - Winton Blount, 10 September 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Jan Boggess, 21 February 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Jan Boggess [1/2], 21 February 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 16)
      - Jan Boggess [2/2], 25 September 1990; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 17)
      - Paul Bowers [1/2], 17 March 1985; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 18)
      - Paul Bowers [2/2], 20 March 1985; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 19)
      - Lola Bradley, 27 February 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Lola Bradley, 27 February 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 20)
      - Gene Bralley, 24 April 2012; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 21)
      - Peter Brennan, 24 March 1975; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Berry Brown [1/2], 1 June 2009; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 22)
      - Berry Brown [2/2], 1 June 2009; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 23)
      - Hez Brown [1/2], 29 October 1985; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 24)
      - Hez Brown [2/2], 29 October 1985; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 25)
      - George Buckingham [1/3], 16 September 1987; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 26)
      - George Buckingham [2/3], 17 July 2002; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 27)
      - George Buckingham [3/3], 17 July 2002; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 28)
      - Duane Buckmaster [1/2], 2 July 1986 - 7 July 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Duane Buckmaster [2/2], 1987 May 22; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Duane Buckmaster [1/3], 2 July 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 29)
      - Duane Buckmaster [2/3], 17 July 1986; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 155, Cassette 30)